ANDRIY NOSOV







+38(067) 909 86 40



nosovandriy@gmail.com



t.me/NosovAndriy



github.com/nosovandriy



linkedin.com/in/andriy-nosov



andriynosov.com

Ternopil, Ukraine | Remote

HARD SKILLS

- JavaScript | TypeScript | HTML | CSS
- React | React Native | Next.js
- SCSS | Tailwind | MUI | Bootstrap
- Rest API | Redux | SQL | Git | Github
- Jest | React Testing Library
- AWS | Vervel | Postman | NPM
- Figma | Jira | SEO | UX/UI

EDUCATION

 Master's degree in Computer **Engineering**

Ternopil Ivan Puluj National Technical University | 2010

 Frontend development Mate Academy | 2022

LANGUAGES

- English B1 (Intermediate)
- Unkrainian Native

ABOUT ME

As a frontend developer, I have a degree in computer engineering and experience with a stack of technologies, including JavaScript, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, React, Next.js, Redux, Rest API, and others.

I have over a year of experience working on commercial projects, both individually and in a team environment, and you can see all of the projects on my portfolio website.

I have good self-learning skills, thanks to which I was able to learn a lot of necessary software and use it effectively in my projects.

My English level is Intermediate, I have good communication skills, which I acquired from a previous job where I worked on a large team and communicated with many clients.

Also, I worked with export documents, which allowed the company to increase its sales and enter the world market. So I can add responsibility and attentiveness to my strong point.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023 COMMERCIAL PROJECTS



Buy Art Help Ukraine — artvswar.gallery



TOOLS: Next.js, TypeScript, HTML, SCSS, Redux, Axios, Stripe, AWS Amplify, AWS Cognito, Cloudinary, React-hook-form, Yup, Swiper.

DESCRIPTION: The "Art vs War" gallery platform is designed to facilitate the sale of paintings, with a focus on merging art and charity. The platform offers possibilities where artists can sell their paintings. Key features of the project include user registration, artist profiles for uploading and editing paintings, and secure sales transactions. This project is based on Next.js and Spring Boot frameworks, utilizing Amazon Web Services and Stripe payment service. Our team consists of a PM, frontend and backend developers, QA, and a UI/UX designer.



CheeseCakes – nahirna-cake.com.ua



TOOLS: Next.js, TypeScript, HTML, Tailwind CSS, Redux, Axios, Swiper, Vercel, Google Analytics, Telegram bot.

DESCRIPTION: E-commerce store with a mobile-first orientation design, built on Next.js. Implemented the ability to receive order data in the Telegram bot and integrated the Google Analytics service.



Ukrainets company – ukrainets.in.ua



TOOLS: Next.js, HTML, SCSS, Swiper, Facebook chat.

DESCRIPTION: An information website for a logistics company with a user-friendly responsive design. Customers have the ability to request a callback, communicate through Facebook chat, and the owner can receive information about customer orders via e-mail.

OTHER PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2021 – Sales Manager (SE Chortkivskyi KHP)

- Implemented the export functionality abroad, which allowed exporting products to the world market;
- Prepared export documents and delivered about 10 thousand tons of goods.

2013 - 2015 — Hardware Sales Manager (Tetra Consulting)

- Bought and sold computer hardware and other related equipment.
- Worked with product vendors. Signed cooperative agreements with new suppliers and expanded the dealer network;

2010 - 2012 – Computer Repair Technician (Tetra Consulting)

• Repaired computer hardware, built and configured PCs.